https://www.heuschenschrouff.com/cookie-policy/

Skip to content
Home About UsAbout H&S Our sales teams Frits Schrouff Foundation Jobs
Brands & ProductsAsian Arab/Turkish African Caribbean Bean Sprouts Retail Foodservice Industry
Order online Contact EnglishNederlands Deutsch
This cookie statement was last updated on 1 April 2020 and applies to citizens of the European Economic Area.
1. Introduction
Our website, https://www.heuschenschrouff.com (hereinafter: “the website”) uses cookies and other related technologies (for convenience all technologies are referred to as “cookies”). Cookies are also placed by third parties we have engaged. In the document below we inform you about the use of cookies on our website.
2. What are cookies?
A cookie is a small simple file that is sent along with pages of this website and stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or another device. The information stored therein may be returned to our servers or to the servers of the relevant third parties during a subsequent visit.
3. What are scripts?
A script is a piece of program code that is used to make our website function properly and interactively. This code is executed on our server or on your device.
4. What is a web beacon?
A web beacon (or a pixel tag) is a small, invisible piece of text or image on a website that is used to monitor traffic on a website. In order to do this, various data about you is stored using web beacons.
5. Consent
When you visit our website for the first time, we will show you a pop-up with an explanation about cookies. As soon as you click on “I agree” or continue, you consent to us using all cookies and plug-ins as described in the pop-up and this cookie statement. You can disable the use of cookies via your browser, but please note that our website may no longer work properly.
6. Cookies
6.1 Technical or functional cookies
Some cookies ensure that certain parts of the website work properly and that your user preferences remain known. By placing functional cookies, we make it easier for you to visit our website. This way, you do not need to repeatedly enter the same information when visiting our website and, for example, the items remain in your shopping cart until you have paid. We may place these cookies without your consent.
6.2 Analytical cookies
We use analytical cookies to optimize the website experience for our users. With these analytical cookies we get insights in the usage of our website. We ask your permission to place analytical cookies.
6.3 Advertising cookies
We do not use any advertising cookies on this website.
6.4 Social media buttons
On our website we have included buttons for Facebook and Instagram to promote webpages (e.g. “like”, “pin”) or share (e.g. “tweet”) on social networks like Facebook and Instagram. These buttons work using pieces of code coming from Facebook and Instagram themselves. This code places cookies. These social media buttons also can store and process certain information, so a personalized advertisement can be shown to you.
Please read the privacy statement of these social networks (which can change regularly) to read what they do with your (personal) data which they process using these cookies. The data that is retrieved is anonymized as much as possible. Facebook and Instagram are located in the United States.
7. Placed cookies
WPML
We use WPML for locale management. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Functional
_icl_current_language
1 day
Store language settings
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.
Google Analytics
We use Google Analytics for website statistics. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Statistics
__utmc
30 minutes
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Analytics Privacy Policy.
YouTube
We use YouTube for video display. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
GPS
session
Sharing
For more information, please read the YouTube Privacy Policy.
Facebook
We use Facebook for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
actppresence
1 year
Manage ad display frequency
_fbc
Sharing
For more information, please read the Facebook Privacy Policy.
8. Your rights with respect to personal data
You have the following rights with respect to your personal data:
You have the right to know why your personal data is needed, what will happen to it, and how long it will be retained for.
Right of access: You have the right to access your personal data that is known to us.
Right to rectification: you have the right to supplement, correct, have deleted or blocked your personal data whenever you wish.
If you give us your consent to process your data, you have the right to revoke that consent and to have your personal data deleted.
Right to transfer your data: you have the right to request all your personal data from the controller and transfer it in its entirety to another controller.
Right to object: you may object to the processing of your data. We comply with this, unless there are justified grounds for processing.
To exercise these rights, please contact us. Please refer to the contact details at the bottom of this cookie statement. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you, but you also have the right to submit a complaint to the supervisory authority (the Data Protection Authority).
9. Enabling/disabling and deleting cookies
You can use your internet browser to automatically or manually delete cookies. You can also specify that certain cookies may not be placed. Another option is to change the settings of your internet browser so that you receive a message each time a cookie is placed. For more information about these options, please refer to the instructions in the Help section of your browser.
Please note that our website may not work properly if all cookies are disabled. If you do delete the cookies in your browser, they will be placed again after your consent when you visit our websites again.
10. Contact details
For questions and/or comments about our cookie policy and this statement, please contact us by using the following contact details:
Heuschen & Schrouff Oriental Foods Trading B.V.
Sperwerweg 1, 6374 AG Landgraaf
Netherlands
Website: https://www.heuschenschrouff.com
Email: info@heuschenschrouff.com
Phone number: +31(0) 45 533 82 00
This cookie policy was synchronized with cookiedatabase.org on 1 April 2020
Heuschen & Schrouff NewsAsia Halal Catalogue26 August 2020Korea Catalogue26 August 2020Spring Happiness2 October 2019Cocoxim2 October 2019Homesoy2 October 2019Roi Thai2 October 2019
Go to Top
This website works so well because we use cookies. With further use you automatically agree to this. Cookie policy I agreeDe cookie-instellingen op deze website zijn ingesteld op 'toestaan cookies "om u de beste surfervaring mogelijk. Als u doorgaat met deze website te gebruiken zonder het wijzigen van uw cookie-instellingen of u klikt op "Accepteren" hieronder dan bent u akkoord met deze instellingen.Sluiten
